

# Laurentiu Big

+40752637400

☑ laurentiubig@gmail.com

### Summary

UTCN Automation and Computers student, interested in anything involving IT

Excellent research, time management and problem solving skills.

Highly organized with the ability to manage multiple projects and consistently meet deadlines.

To have a better look at my projects, I suggest looking through my github profile: https://github.com/laurentiubig

Github Website: https://laurentiubig.github.io/

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/big-laurentiu-304598165/

## **Core Competencies**

Self-Learner

Initiative

Flexibility

Team Building / Leadership

**Analytical Thinking** 

Stress Management

Conceptual Thinking

Thoroughness

#### Education

#### **Automation and Computers in English**

2017 - 2021

**UTCN** Automatics and Computers

I had chose this field in favor of computer science and automation because I wanted to learn hardware as well as software

#### **Mathematics and Informatics**

2013 - 2017

Liceul Teoretic Lucian Blaga Cluj Napoca

#### Work experience

#### **Fullstack Developer**

2019-10 - 2020-04

Paddy Power Betfair

It was a new and positive experience working at Betfair, I was surrounded with a fun environment and great people who taught me some new concepts for :

Backend - Java with the following technologies: maven, sping.

Fronted - mostly VueJs, Angular and some ReactJs.

QA testing - with the following technologies: Junit, selenium, mockito, jenkins, Jest

Scrum agile methodology.

Arhitecture of deployment environment - build and deploy artifacts. Web server load management

**Web Developer** 2018-05 - 2019-05

Simbound

etc

While working at Simbound I helped in winning the EdTech award for Content marketing Simulation in 2018:

• https://startupeuropeawards.eu/simbound-is-the-romanian-winner-of-the-edtech-category/ and implemented new features for the Simbound Simulation using the following technologies:

HTML, CSS ,PHP ,MySQL JavaScript, jQuery, React .

Work in team using Git for version control

Come with new ideas for making the experience as pleasant as possible

Configure the server for my needs(Ex. git deployment)

# Skills React with Redux, Graphql and Apollo Server Angular Js VueJs PHP & MySql Junit, Jest Java JavaScript, JQuery HTML & CSS Git C C#, C++ Linear Algebra, Calculus and Geometry

English Language Level



#### Courses I followed

https://www.udemy.com/course/the-complete-guide-to-angular-2/

https://www.udemy.com/course/complete-react-developer-zero-to-mastery/

https://www.linkedin.com/learning/learning-spring-with-spring-boot-2

# Interests/Hobbies

- -Video Games
- -Fitness/Gym
- -Reading books, Comics
- -Movies, Tv shows

